Dan Carson

425-802-2952 / dan@okdan.com / okdan.com Oakland, CA



Summary

I'm an experienced design lead who believes design can make a positive difference in people's lives. Over the past 14 years, I've worked at startups, on a Presidential campaign, at agencies, and consulted with both non-profits and corporations. I love to collaborate and work cross-functionally to build products that deliver value, and ultimately make an impact in the world.

Experience

Crowdpac – San Francisco, CA Head of Design and User Experience

08/2015 - Present

Senior member of the product development team where I plan, research, design, build, and test tools that give people around the world a new way to participate in the political process and make an impact.

okdan.com – Everywhere Design consultant 03/2015 - 8/2015

As a design consultant, I've worked with great organizations like Change.org, Trunk Club, Hillary for America, Northwestern University, Planned Parenthood, and many more.

Modest, Inc. – Chicago, IL Senior Product Designer

02/2014 - 02/2015

Senior Product Designer in charge of UX, interaction design, and user testing. I was responsible for the user experience of our native iOS and Android apps, new retailer onboarding, and store management tools.

Change.org – San Francisco, CA Product Designer, Contract

07/2013 - 11/2013

Focused on the initial public launch of Change.org for Decision Makers - a revolutionary new tool that enables two-way dialog between elected officials and their constituents via the world's most popular online petition platform.

Trunk Club – Chicago, IL Product Designer, Contract 02/2013 - 07/2013

Worked on a wide range of products, including optimization of the customer acquisition flow, redesigning the iPhone app, redesigning the public website, and helping implement brand guidelines across multiple platforms.

Experience cont'd

Trunk Club – Chicago, IL Product Designer, Contract

02/2013 - 07/2013

Worked on a wide range of products, including optimization of the customer acquisition flow, redesigning the iPhone app, redesigning the public website, and helping implement brand guidelines across multiple platforms.

Obama for America - Chicago, IL

11/2012 - 02/2013

Design Director

As OFA transitioned from a campaign to a non-profit I managed two other designers, and worked closely with our development and content teams to oversee the delivery of design products supporting the President's agenda.

Obama for America - Chicago, IL

10/2011 - 11/2012

Lead Interactive Designer

Worked alongside the most talented and passionate group of people I've ever had the pleasure of meeting. I collaborated every day with our field organization, technology, and digital teams to create tools and experiences that engaged with supporters, raised money, and earned votes.

Hornall Anderson Design Works – Seattle, WA

11/2009 - 09/2011

Interactive Designer

Interactive design and development, motion graphics, and thoughtful UX for clients like Madison Square Garden, Empire State Building, HTC, Microsoft, Pepsico, and Hewlett Packard.

POP - Seattle, WA

10/2006 - 05/2009

Designer and Frontend developer

I designed, built, and launched micro-sites, rich media banner campaigns, motion graphics, and 3d work for clients like Nintendo, EA, XBOX, Target, and Ubisoft.

Squad Studios – Seattle, WA Designer and Frontend developer

03/2004 - 04/2006

Designer, developer, and wearer of all possible hats. We built websites, music videos, and e-commerce products for some of your favorite bands.

Education

The Art Institute of Seattle

2002 - 2004

AAA, Interactive Media Development

Dean's List, Alumni Hall of Fame, and occasional speaker.

Awards

1st Place at Hack4Congress DC, Seattle Show 2009, The FWA 2008, ADDY 2008, IAB Interactive Awards 2007